Right now we have marketing and sales.
If we did the cost, you would see
all of the structure, all of the information
that the AI was able to generate, from
the metadata to some details.
Then we have modules.
At the end of the day, that's over
one hour, 20 minutes worth of costs.
The AI splitted it into five modules, and
each of the modules have their own lessons.
So if we look at what we have,
you would see that we have all our
modules here.
And when you check each of the modules,
you see that the videos are not there.
Then the assessment, of course, the AI came
up with the assessment.
You have the assessment here.
You can see the question, came up with
the question, the options, everything set.
And it did that for all the modules.
You go through the modules, you see you
have three lessons, you have one assessment.